♬ 惹きあわせる
Shijima no soko kara
From out of the stillness
♬ 受け継ぐ愛を 宿命と呼ぶなら
Timing:
Fadeout4
♬ 微笑む目で 次の手を
Mezameru sono hashira tachi
The Pillars of the past are awakening
Editor:
Tonitonichopchop
Toki wo koe
To the dawn of a new day
Editor:
Tonitonichopchop
Shinku no chishio ga
The river of crimson blood within you
♬ 闇を欺いて
刹那を躱して
Fadeout4
Typesetting:
♬ 刃すり抜け奴らの間隙を突け
Mazrim
Quality Check:
Tachiagaru yuuki wo hikiawaseru
Carries with it the courage to stand and fight
♬ つらぬいた信念が 未来を拓く
Uketsugu ai wo sadame to yobu nara
Even if the love I feel is just part of my legacy...
♬ Like a Bloody Storm
熱くLike a Bloody Stone
♬ 血脈に
刻まれた因縁に
Hohoemu me de tsugi no te wo
I'll still be smiling as I stay one step ahead
♬ 浮き上がる消えない誇りの絆
♬ 握りしめて
Yami wo azamuite setsuna wo kawashite
Defying the darkness and dodging death at every turn
Encoding:
Fadeout4
Yaiba surinuke yatsura no suki wo tsuke
Slipping past the knife's edge and striking when you least expect
Tsuranuita omoi ga mirai wo hiraku
The emotions running through me blaze a path to the future...
Raw Hunter: WRRRRY
Like a bloody storm
Atsuku like a bloody storm
Burning like a bloody storm
Ketsumyaku ni kizamareta innen ni
When the time comes to end the vendetta carried by our blood
Distro:
ExWizzard
Ukiagaru kienai hokori no kizuna
Remember that the bonds of pride will carry you through any storm
Nigirishimete
So hold them close
http://www.some-stuffs.com
Episode 23: "The Warrior of Wind"
(ｼﾞｮｾﾌ)ううっ… か… 風が…｡
T-That wind... It's flowing toward Wham...
何だ…？
ワムウの方へ寄っていく｡
Final Mode...
(ﾜﾑｳ)最終流法 渾楔颯！
Perfect Storm!
ううっ！
うっ… こ… これは風か!?
T-That's just wind?!
You're near the flame...
炎のそばゆえ➡
so I only know your approximate location, Jojo.
ジョジョ 貴様の
おおよその位置しか分からぬ｡
しかし 波紋の呼吸を止めた今➡
But now that you can't use the Ripple, I'll find you eventually...
１cmずつ 次第に
必ず 貴様の体を捉え➡
...and cut you down.
切断していくだろう｡
(ｶｰｽﾞ)《渾楔颯
ワムウの最終流法》
Perfect Storm is Wham's final mode.
《姿を透明にするとき使った
管より➡
The pipes he uses to cloak himself suck up huge amounts of air...
逆に 膨大な量の風を 取り込み
肺の中で 超圧縮させる｡➡
...and then compress it.
The air is then blasted out of a paper-thin slit.
そして かみそりのような
極限に狭い隙間から➡
超高圧で噴き出す｡
いわば 烈風のメス！➡
It is a razor made of wind.
But it creates a terrible amount of heat and friction, even for Wham.
しかし！
風の高速圧縮に伴う 摩擦や熱は➡
いくら ワムウといえど
その肉体は 耐え切れず➡
His body can't handle it, so he's falling apart.
どんどん 崩れていくのみ》
But that tragic figure is truly breathtaking.
(ｶｰｽﾞ)しかし
その 無残なる姿 美しいぞ｡➡
Victory is yours! Take his life to ease your wounds!
勝つのは お前だ！
勝って 人間どもの生命で➡
その傷を癒やそうぞ！
(ﾘｻﾘｻ)ジョジョ！
Jojo!
I-It's close!
き… 来た｡
これに対する策を
何か 出さなくては！
I'll have to use one of my tricks!
《名付けて 波紋オイル作戦｡➡
This one's called the Ripple oil trick!
His lungs are like high-pressure oxygen tanks.
や… やつの体内は
いわば 超圧縮酸素ボンベだ！➡
Those pipes...
あの胸の管
この火炎瓶を たたきつければ➡
If I can hit them...
...he'll suck in the flames and explode!
やつは 火を吸い込んで
体内で爆発する！➡
But this could be my final plot...
しかし これは 俺の
ファイナルプロットでもある｡➡
If I mess this up...
しくじれば やられる！》
うわ～っ！
NWWW！ いたな そこか!?
I've got you now!
Blast it!
くそ～！ 食らえ ワムウ！
Take this, Wham!
ぬっ！
ああっ！
A firebomb?
火炎瓶か くだらん｡
Pathetic.
I can sense things that are away from the flames.
炎から １ｍも離れれば
物体は感知できる｡➡
You're out of tricks.
策は尽きたようだな｡➡
And that cry gave away your position.
そして 今のうめき声で
貴様の位置が分かった｡
ううっ…｡
Now...
(ﾜﾑｳ)いくぞ 渾楔颯！
Perfect Storm!
Caesar!
シーザー！
Lend me your aid!
頼むぜ～！
More fire?
(ﾜﾑｳ)また 火炎をよこすのか？➡
何度やっても
１ｍ近づけば 感知できる｡
I can sense things away from the flames.
ぐあっ！
そして➡
And now I will cut you in half to claim my victory!
このまま 貴様を切断すれば決着！
Jojo!
ジョジョ！
や… やっと勝ったか｡
H-He's finally won it.
ワムウ｡
Wham...
今の シーザーのバンダナ攻撃で
もはや お前は負けている｡
You lost the moment I threw Caesar's bandana.
ぬっ!?
Don't you see I meant for you to break the bottle?
火炎瓶は あえて 割らせるために
投げたのが 分からないのか!?
Your ability to cut it so easily led to your defeat.
お前の能力が 瓶を
あっさり カットできたことが➡
敗北につながったのだ！
The oil that was inside is now vapor.
油は
体内で 霧状のガスになっている｡
And Caesar's bandana that you sliced up?
そして こま切れになった
シーザーのバンダナは！
The fire... it's still burning!
(ﾜﾑｳ)火… 火が消えていない｡
その火も 吸い込まれる｡
And I'm sucking it in!
Wham...
ワムウ
貴様は 戦士としては すごかった｡
You were an incredible fighter.
But a powerful ally named Caesar was with me this whole time.
だが 俺には シーザーという➡
強い味方が
最後まで ついていたのさ｡
(ﾜﾑｳ)ぐおっ！
H-He lost.
(吸血鬼１)ま… 負けた｡
He lost!
(吸血鬼２)負けた ワムウ様が…｡
(ｶｰｽﾞ)うぬ…｡
Master Wham!
あう… うう… うっ…｡
あっ…｡
はぁ… はぁ…｡
ジョジョ！
やつは 爆発程度では➡
Jojo, that creature can regenerate, even after exploding.
粉々になっても 復元する生物｡
Use your strongest Ripple to finish him completely!
最も強いとされる
拳からの波紋で 消滅させるのよ！
(ﾜﾑｳ)
つ… ついに 決着がついたな｡
S-So it's finally over, Jojo...
ジョ… ジョ…｡
It is.
ああ｡
You have avenged Caesar.
シーザーのあだを討ったな｡
そうとも｡
I did.
Then do it.
では やるがいい とどめを…｡
Finish me.
I will!
そうかい！
はっ！
W-What is this?!
な… 何のまねだ!?
That smoke isn't from the explosion.
その煙は 爆発の煙ではない｡
それは 波紋傷の煙だ！
It's from your wounds.
The Ripple from your limbs spread throughout your body.
先に 胸や足に食らった波紋は
既に 全身に回っていたようだな｡
お前らにとって➡
I know how painful the Ripple must be for your kind.
波紋が どんなに苦しいかは
よく知っている｡
もう 治すことはできねえが➡
I cannot mend you.
俺の血で
せめて 痛みを和らげて死にな｡
But my blood can ease your pain before you go.
Do you wish to shame the great Wham as he dies?
貴様！ このワムウに
生き恥をかかせる気か!?
Stop! I don't need your pity!
やめろ
敵からの情けなど 要らん！
情け？
今 お前は ｢情け｣と言ったのか？
Pity?
Did you say "pity?"
なら なぜ お前は
シーザーのバンダナと➡
Tell me, why did you ignore the bubble that carried Caesar's bandana and this piercing?
やつの心である この解毒剤の
ピアスの入った シャボン玉を➡
割らずに 残しておいたんだ？
情けからか？
Was it pity?
It was because that man was an honorable warrior.
それは あの男が
誇り高き戦士だったからだ｡
I wished to honor him!
戦士への敬意のためだ！
はっ！
｢まさか ジョジョ 貴様！｣と驚く｡
"No, Jojo, you don't..." is what you'll say next.
No, Jojo, you don't...
(ﾜﾑｳ)まさか ジョジョ 貴様！
I do, Wham.
そうさ ワムウ
戦いは 戦いで別｡
A fight is a fight.
シーザーの死の悲しみは
悲しみで別｡
My grief for Caesar is mine to deal with.
俺も なぜか あんたに対して
敬意を払いたくなったのさ｡
Somehow, I wanted to honor you in return.
この血は あんたへの敬意なんだ｡
My blood pays tribute to you.
フフ…｡ 完敗だよ ジョジョ｡
どうやら お前は➡
I have completely lost, Jojo.
It seems that as a warrior, you stand taller than I ever did.
俺より 戦士としても
高みに立ったようだな…｡
(吸血鬼３)ぶ… ぶち殺せ～！
Kill the bastard!
(吸血鬼たち)うお～！
Halt!
(ﾜﾑｳ)待て～い！
貴様ら 何をする気だ!?
What betrayal is this?!
What?!
なっ!?
You filth!
この外道どもが！
(吸血鬼２)うわ～！
ワムウ！
Wham!
な… なぜ!?
W-Why?
この ワムウ➡
I am sworn to Master Cars, but I will not allow the vampires to attack you.
最期まで カーズ様の味方だが➡
吸血鬼どもには 手出しを許さん｡
シーザーにも言ったが 決して
センチになったからではない｡
I told Caesar this as well.
It's not because I am sentimental.
この ワムウにとって
強者だけが真理｡
To me, strength itself gives rise to righteousness.
Victory alone is just and admirable.
勝者だけが 正義であり友情｡
I merely lived according to my own code of honor, Jojo.
その 自分自身のおきてに
従っただけのことだ｡
ジョジョ このワムウ➡
To me, immortality was a trivial thing.
今までの人生 不老不死など
どうでも よかったのだ｡
All that mattered was living up to my code.
この おきてさえ貫いて
朽ち果てられればな｡
ああ…｡
さあ｡
Now...
Drink the antidote for me.
解毒剤を飲んでみせてくれ｡
Do it before I fade.
俺が 消滅してしまわないうちに｡
分かるのか？
Will you see?
I don't need eyes, a horn, or words.
触覚も目も言葉も 要らない｡
伝わるよ｡ 動作だけで十分だ｡
I will know.
The action is what matters.
(ﾜﾑｳ)悔いはない｡
I have no regrets.
I am glad I was able to witness your growth.
心から お前の成長が見れて
よかったと思うよ｡
俺は お前に出会うために➡
Perhaps I lived these thousands of years just to meet you at the end.
１万数千年も
さまよってたのかもしれぬ｡
Fare...well...
さら… ば… だ…
ジョ… ジョ…｡
Jo...jo...
(ﾅﾚｰｼｮﾝ)〈ワムウは風になった｡➡
Wham returned to the wind.
Jojo immediately gave his opponent a last salute.
ジョジョが 無意識のうちに
取っていたのは➡
敬礼の姿であった｡➡
Though he shed no tears, they had shared an unspoken bond.
涙は流さなかったが
無言の男の詩があった｡➡
奇妙な友情があった〉
A bizarre friendship.
Wham, kill him.
(ｶｰｽﾞ)
《ワムウ そいつを殺すのだ》
(ﾜﾑｳ)《し… しかし カーズ様｡➡
B-But Master Cars...
お言葉ですが
相手は 少年でございまする》
With respect, he's only a boy.
A boy? That he is.
《｢少年｣… そうだ｡➡
That's why he must die.
だから
なおさら 殺さねばならぬ｡➡
波紋の戦士の子は
大人になったら➡
If these Ripple warriors grow up, they'll be deadly enemies.
強大な 天敵となるやもしれぬ｡➡
人間は
あっという間に 成長する》
And humans grow quite rapidly.
《うう…》
《できぬのか!? ワムウ！➡
Can you do it, Wham?
Well, since you can't do it yourself...
そうか
お前にできぬというのならば➡
では 見本を見せてやろう｡➡
...let me show you how.
This is how it's done, Wham!
こうやるのだ！ ワムウ！》
(ｶｰｽﾞ)ワムウ！
Wham...
He was too pure a warrior.
やつは 戦闘者として
あまりにも 純粋すぎた！
That purity made him weak!
それが 弱さにつながったのだ！
(吸血鬼３)
おい ワムウのやつが負けたぜ｡
Hey, Wham just lost!
(吸血鬼４)
けっ 何だ がっかりさせるぜ｡
Keh! What a disappointment.
(吸血鬼５)
バカが カッコつけやがって｡
That fool thought he was a big deal.
Your underlings are so disrespectful, it makes me want to puke.
確かに こいつらは
クズの集まりね｡ ヘドが出るわ｡
(吸血鬼たち)ああっ！
あ… あ… カーズ様｡
Master Cars...
H-He's drinking us.
す… 吸い取られる…｡
残るは このカーズ １人か｡
Now only I remain.
(ｶｰｽﾞ)
だが 頂点に立つ者は 常に １人！
However...
I alone always stand on top!
Look at Lord Cars!
(吸血鬼１)カーズ様が！
おおっ！ カーズ様が～！
Lord Cars is...!
He's ready to fight!
(吸血鬼２)戦闘態勢に入った～！
But Lord Cars, there's no reason to fight one-on-one!
(吸血鬼３)しかし カーズ様！
わざわざ １対１で
決闘する必要はありませぬ！
Who needs rules? Let us take them!
(吸血鬼４)ルール無用！
やはり 我々が こいつらを！
We'll turn them into sprays of blood!
(吸血鬼５)血しぶく
ズタボロと化すのが 一番～！
I thought you'd do this!
やはり来るか てめえら！
あっ…｡
(吸血鬼３)ぐっ！
(吸血鬼４)がっ！
言ったはずだわ！
(吸血鬼６)はっ！
I told you!
(吸血鬼７)はっ！
(吸血鬼８)せ… 赤石！
T-The Red Stone!
ルールは カーズ対私の １対１｡
It's me against Cars, one-on-one.
でも あえて
約束を破るというのなら➡
But if you don't like those terms,
この赤石を 砕き散らすのみ！
I'll just smash it!
約束は守る｡
I'm a man of my word.
One-on-one.
１対１
破るつもりは 初めからない｡
My promise still stands.
だから この頭巾を取って
触角を見せたのだ｡
That's why I revealed my horn to you.
As for my underlings' behavior, they're already dead, as you can see.
そのクズどもの 勝手な行動は➡
そいつらを 既に
殺していることから 分かるはず｡
(吸血鬼６･吸血鬼７)んっ!?
(吸血鬼８)カーズ様!?
Master Cars?!
(ｶｰｽﾞ)俺の目的は その赤石｡
All I want is that Red Stone.
しかし エシディシと ワムウは
１万年以上も 共に生きた仲間｡
However, Wham and AC/DC were my comrades for 10,000 years.
I must honor both their deaths and their pride.
彼らの死と 誇り高き戦いへの
思いは 貫き通す必要がある｡➡
I will fight you Ripple warriors fairly...
貴様ら 波紋の戦士には
どうしても 正々堂々➡
この手で 決着をつけたくなった！
...and finish this with my own hands.
And Lisa Lisa, after seeing you fight, I no longer think of you as a woman.
それに リサリサ 今の戦いぶり｡
もう お前を 女とは思わん｡
このカーズ
全能力を注ぎ込んで 倒してやる｡
I will fight you with all my strength.
Come!
(ｶｰｽﾞ)ついてこい！
次なる決闘場は あそこだ｡
We fight over there.
The temple at Piz Berlina.
(ｶｰｽﾞ)
ピッツベルリナ山 神殿遺跡！
(ｶｰｽﾞ)かつて
下の戦車戦競技場の 優勝者が➡
Champions once came here to drink the blood of the fallen mixed with liquor.
この神殿で 敗者の血を
お神酒に混ぜて 飲み干し➡
生命の喜びを 神に感謝した場所｡
They thanked the gods for the joy of life.
It's not an arena, but it will add to our fight.
(ｶｰｽﾞ)闘技場ではないが
立体的な戦闘が 楽しめよう｡
M-Master Lisa Lisa, you may be strong, but you're still a woman.
リ… リサリサ先生！
いくら強くっても
やはり あんたは女｡
やつは ワムウより弱そうだし
俺が 戦うぜ！
He looks weaker than Wham. I'll take him!
You won't.
無用｡
たかが 20歳前の小僧から
いたわられるほど➡
I haven't lived my life so that a teenage brute has to stand up for me.
やわな人生は 送っていない｡
T-That's some fifty year old!
さ… さすが50歳｡
(ｶｰｽﾞ)俺には
流法 輝彩滑刀がある｡➡
I will use my Brilliant Bone Blade mode.
I would offend Wham if I didn't offer you a weapon.
お前に 武器を与えねば➡
ワムウの誇り高い意志を
汚すことになる｡
そこの好きな武器を選べ｡
Take your pick.
この 自分のマフラーで十分｡
My scarf will suffice.
I see.
そうか…｡ では 来い｡
Then let us fight.
《こ… このカーズの構えは
殺気がない》
T-There's no aggression in Cars' stance.
《殺気を発さないで
戦えるのか…？》
How can he fight without aggression?
どうした？ 来ないのか？
What's wrong? Not coming?
では こちらから行くぞ！
Then I'll have to make the first move!
はっ｡
Cars disappeared with that light!
カーズが ちょっとした光と共に
消えたぞ！
ど… どこだ!?
W-Where is he?!
Cars... I can feel something...
カーズの… こ… この気配は!?
But it's coming from both above and below.
う… 上から来るようでいて
下から来るようでもある｡
♬～
Brilliant Bone Blade mode!
流法 輝彩滑刀！
柱の ひびの中から!?
A crack in the pillar!
Snake Scarf!
蛇首立帯！
This Satiporoja beetle scarf is a perfect Ripple conductor.
このマフラーは
ｻﾃｨﾎﾟﾛｼﾞｱ･ﾋﾞｰﾄﾙという虫の➡
100％ 波紋を伝える糸で
編んだもの｡
波紋の武器であり
生命反応のレーダー！
It is a weapon and a life-detector!
It even picks up attacks from behind!
背後からの攻撃をも 感知できる！
アブ！
OGOOOHHHHH！
S-She did it!
や… やった～！
やっぱり先生 すげえぜ！
That's my master! Wonderful!
ワムウに比べりゃあ
あっけないが➡
He didn't compare to Wham, but barkers seldom bite!
威張ってるやつは
案外 あんなもの｡
Though you are better than me, master!
先生の実力は
俺以上ということもあるが！
うあっ…｡
なっ！
Wha—?!
カ… カーズ様～！
M-Master Cars!
カ… カーズが後ろに…｡
Cars is behind her.
Who is b-below her?
下の野郎は だ… 誰だ!?
W-What the...?!
な… 何だ!?
一体 何なんだ～!?
What the hell is going on?!
Cars wasn't the one fighting!
戦っていたのは カーズじゃねえ！
影武者だ！
It was a double!
うっ…｡
(ｶｰｽﾞ)ふん くだらんなあ｡
How utterly stupid.
Why would I fight one-on-one?
１対１の決闘なんてなあ｡
このカーズの目的は
あくまでも 赤石｡
All I want is the Red Stone.
あくまでも 究極生物になること｡
My goal is to be the ultimate life form.
ワムウのような戦士に
なるつもりもなければ➡
I am not a warrior like Wham, nor am I a romantic.
ロマンチストでもない｡➡
No matter what the method, in the end...
どんな手を使おうが 最終的に…｡
勝てば よかろうなのだ～！
...victory is all that matters!
ぐあっ！
《ど… 道理で
殺気がないはず…｡➡
T-That's why I felt no aggression.
He never intended to fight me himself.
自分で戦う意思は
最初から なかった… のね…》
It's over!
とどめ！
ジョ… ジョ…｡
Jo... jo...
The Red Stone is mine!
赤石は 手に入れた！➡
Now all that's left is for all of you to kill that annoying Jojo!
あとは
その うるさいジョジョのやつを➡
お前ら全員で 始末せよ～！
うお～‼
C-Cars!
カ… カーズ！
I'll make you pay for this!
許さねえ！
(吸血鬼たち)うわ～！
Cars!
カーズ～！
Out of the way! I'll split your damned skulls!
てめえら どきやがれ！
脳天 ぶっ砕くぜ！ おのれら！
Zoom Punch!
ズームパンチ！
(吸血鬼)うっ！
う… ううっ｡
Your Ripple isn't working.
波紋が あんまし効かねえぜ｡
弱まってるぜ こいつ…
He's weakened! Now—
波紋肘支疾走！
Rebuff Overdrive!
はぁ… はぁ…｡
(ｶｰｽﾞ)相当の疲労が
残ってるようだなあ｡➡
You look worn out.
呼吸も乱れ始めて
波紋効果が 弱まってるぞ｡➡
Your breathing is ragged and your Ripple is weak.
いかに このリサリサに師事し
成長した波紋も➡
And you're all that's left of the Ripple-users Lisa Lisa trained.
これだけの人数➡
Will you last?
続くか？➡
Will you last, Jojo?
続くか～？ ジョジョ｡
Will... you... last?
続･くゥ･カァ？
(吸血鬼たち)は～っ！
(吸血鬼)グフフッ｡
こ… この野郎…｡
S-Son of a...
Flay him alive!
バラ肉にしちまえ～！
ヤ… ヤベえ…｡
C-Crap!
ぬっ!? うわっ…｡
ん？
こ… この光は!?
T-That light!
その顔は!?
That face!
Listen up, vampires!
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)おのれら 吸血鬼！
このシュトロハイムと
ドイツ軍精鋭部隊が 相手だ！
You're up against Stroheim and the German elite!
And we're the Speedwagon Foundation Special Forces!
(一同)我ら スピードワゴン財団
特別科学戦闘隊もいるぞ！
Jojo!
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)ジョジョ！
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)ジョジョ！
Jojo!
I-It's Speedwagon!
ス… スピードワゴンのじいさん！
And Smokey from New York!
そして お前は
ニューヨークの スモーキー！
フッ｡
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)ヘヘ｡
フフフ ちょいと 右足が
ギクシャクするがァァァァ！
My right leg is a bit stiff...
...but my body has been repaired!
俺の体は 修理は完了ォォォォォ｡
そして 食らえ！
新しい 対吸血鬼兵器！➡
Now taste our anti-vampire weaponry!
紫外線照射装置ィィィ！
Ultraviolet lasers!
(吸血鬼たち)ぐぺぽっ｡
Even though the Speedwagon Foundation were the ones to miniaturize those lamps...
小型化に成功したのは
我々 スピードワゴン財団なのに➡
うぬぼれの強い男だな｡
(一同)いけ～！
ふん… こざかしい人間どもが｡
Crafty little creatures.
ん？
ジョジョ どこだ？
やつがいない！
Where is Jojo?
He's gone!
ん!?
You're as quick as ever.
相変わらず
すばしっこいやつだな｡
ちょっと目を離すと➡
I take my eyes off you for a moment, and you've already come up with a new scheme.
すぐ 抜け目のない行動を
取っている｡
てめえは 超えてはならねえ
一線を 超えた｡
You crossed a line you shouldn't have crossed.
You said you'd fight fairly, but you cheated Lisa Lisa!
てめえは 正々堂々と言いながら
リサリサをだまし 裏切った！
That act betrayed the memory of Wham, your fallen comrade!
そして てめえの その行為は➡
仲間であった ワムウの意志をも
裏切ったんだ！
You can save your indignation, scum.
このカスが…
激高するんじゃあない…｡
目的を達するというのが
至上のこと｡
The end justifies the means.
あくまで
赤石を 手に入れればよいのだ！
All that matters is the Red Stone.
できるだけ 汗をかかず
危険を最小限にし➡
You have to save effort, minimize danger,
avoid risks, and move your pawns carefully.
ばくちを避け
戦いの駒を 一手一手 動かす｡
That is a real battle.
それが 真の戦闘だ！➡
And now I'll maneuver you into my hands and to your death.
貴様も 今から じわじわと
俺の手の内に ハマって➡
死んでいくことになる｡
Let me tell you something, Cars!
俺は！ お前ほど… カーズ！
I've never hated anyone as much as you!
真底 心から
憎いと思ったやつはいねえ！
You hate me?
憎いだと？
晴らしてみろ ジョジョ！
Then do something about it, Jojo!
A one-on-one duel.
I'll give you that one-on-one duel you wanted so badly!
１対１だぞ｡
望んでいた １対１の戦いだ！
うう…｡
はっ…｡
(ｶｰｽﾞ)フフフ リサリサは
ほとんど死んでいる｡➡
Lisa Lisa is almost dead...
But she is still barely hanging on.
だが ちょっぴり生きている｡
Of course, I intentionally injured her without killing her.
あえて そうした｡ ちょっぴりだけ
生かしておいた｡➡
Do you know why?
なぜだと思う？➡
Because she's another one of my pawns.
この女は ｢駒｣だ！➡
Jojo, she will be the pawn I use to defeat you.
ジョジョ
貴様を詰む ｢駒｣の１個だ！
(ｶｰｽﾞ)
ウィン ウィン ウィン ウィン…｡
フフフ…｡
ウィン ウィン ウィン ウィーン
ウィン…｡
Bastard!
この野郎！
はあっ！
あっ！
I've sewn her feet together with this rope, Jojo!
(ｶｰｽﾞ)ロープを通して
両足を縫い付けたぞ｡
ジョジョ！➡
なぜ こんなことをすると思う？
Why am I doing this?
Here's why!
それは！
リ… リサリサ～！
Lisa Lisa!
(ｶｰｽﾞ)そ～ら！➡
Off you go!
落としてしまっては
駒にならぬ｡➡
She'd be a bad pawn if she falls to her death!
ロープをつかまぬと
地面に激突して➡
If you don't grab the rope, she'll splatter on the ground and die, Jojo!
死んでしまうぞ ジョジョ！
フハハハハ…｡
む…｡
ジョ… ジョジョ！ リサリサ！
J-Jojo! Lisa Lisa!
え？ ｢リサリサ｣？
Lisa Lisa?
That Lisa Lisa?
｢リサリサ｣って
エリナおばあちゃんから聞いた➡
Do you mean the baby on the ship Granny Erina told us about?
船の事故から
助け育てたっていう赤ちゃん？
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)す… すると あの人が!?➡
T-That means that woman is Jojo's...
ジョジョの…｡
Now you're glued to that spot.
もう お前は そこから動けない｡
これが 真の戦闘だ ジョジョ！
Welcome to a real battle, Jojo.
このカーズは
こうやって 何気なく近づき➡
I'll just walk up to you and slice you down while you can't move!
動きを封じられた貴様を
切り刻むのみ！
うお～‼ 貴様 カーズ！
Cars, you bastard!
I hope you rot in hell forever!
どこまでも 腐り切ってやがる！
《ジョジョは 知らないんだ｡➡
Jojo doesn't know.
He doesn't know that that woman is his own mother!
あの女の人が
自分の母親であるということを》
♬(ｴﾝﾃﾞｨﾝｸﾞﾃｰﾏ)
♬ I'll be the roundabout
I'll be the roundabout
♬ The words
will make you out'n'out
The words will make you out 'n' out
I'll spend the day your way
♬ I spend the day away
Call it morning driving through the sound and
♬ Call it morning
driving through
♬ the sound and
in and out the valley
In and out the valley
♬～
♬ The music dance and sing
The music dance and sing
They make the children really ring
♬ They make
the children really ring
I'll spend the day your way
♬ Spend the day away
Call it morning driving through the sound and
♬ Call it morning
driving through
♬ the sound and
in and out the valley
In and out the valley
In and around the lake
♬ In and around the lake
Mountains come out of the sky
♬ Mountains come out of
the sky and they stand there
and they stand there
One mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
♬ One mile over we'll be there
and we'll see you
Ten true summers we'll be there and laughing too
♬ Ten true summers
♬ we'll be there
and laughing too
♬ Twenty four before
my love you'll see
Twenty four before my love you'll see I'll be
♬ I'll be there with you
There with you
Next Episode
Are the vampires finished?!
I want to kill you at my leisure.
The fire is a gamble!
This child... This child...
Stop it, Stroheim!
Oh, no!
Episode 24:
"The Link to Jojo"
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
まだ 吸血鬼は片づかないのか!?
(ｶｰｽﾞ)俺は 楽をして
貴様を殺したいのだ！
この火は賭けだ！
(ｴﾘﾅ)この子は… この子だけは…｡
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
やめろ！ シュトロハイム！
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)しまった～！